Guide to the Jane Lathrop Stanford Papers SC0033B
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Correspondence, 1868-1905; Series 1; 6 Linear Feet
  - Incoming
    - Camerino, M., 1901-1904 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - ALS enclosing contracts, 1902 Sep 23
      - ALS progress on mosaics in Church and Museum, would like her comments on them, 1902 Sep 25
      - ALS working on her request for sky in background of Church mosaic, 1902 Oct 8
      - tel confirming width of pictures, 1902 Nov 5
      - ALS re difficulty between Zampatto and McGilvray, 1902 Nov 11
      - tel re pictures left, 1902 Dec 2
      - ALS seasonal greetings, travel plans, 1903 Jan 1
      - ALS sorry to miss her in Venice, is leaving soon for California, 1904 Apr 30
      - ts copy of telegram re drawings for mosaics in Nave, undated
    - Carr, Austie L., 1894-1895 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - ALS awaiting birth of her baby, asks for a RR pass, 1894 Jan 12
      - ALS named her son Leland, 1894 Mar 22
      - ALS living in San Francisco, would like to call on her, 1895 Dec 1
    - Carr, Lizzie M., 1895-1896 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - ALS thinking of her on anniversary of Leland's death, 1895 June 21
      - ALS congratulations on government suit, 1895 June 30
      - congratulations on government suit, son at Stanford, undated Mar 1896?
    - Carter, M.C.W., 1894-1896 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - ALS re her efforts to obtain a pension, 1894 Sep 10
      - ALS personal news, death of a brother-in-law, Christian Science, Mrs. Hearst at a meeting, her husband was both Rear Admiral and Major General, 1895 Mar 14
      - ALS congratulations on government suit, 1896 Mar 3
    - Casanova, Father A. D., 1891-1892 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - ALS re arrangements for unveiling of Fr. Junipero statue in Monterey; includes letter to Casanova from Society of California Pioneers of May 21, 1891, May 24, 1891
      - ALS thanks for gift of wine, May 26, 1891
      - ALS received her gifts, July 31, 1891
      - ALS has offered prayers for her and husband, Feb 17, 1892
      - ALS has photos of Fr. Junipero to help the sculptor, undated
    - Choate, Joseph H., 1895-1896 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - ALS will call tomorrow, 1895 May 1
      - ALS advises her to make new will and consider other matters re University, 1896 Feb 9
      - Tel. congratulations, 1896 Mar 2
      - ALS approves of her letter to Crocker, 1896 Mar 25
    - Cleveland, 1895-1896 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Cleveland, Grover, ALS and cvr. to Richard Olney introducing Mrs. Stanford, Apr 30, 1895
      - Cleveland, Frances F., ALS Thank you and personal invitation, Oct 29, 1895
      - Cleveland, Miss, A.N. on calling card, undated
      - Cleveland's secretary to P. L. Crovat, Vina, thanks for Mrs. Stanford's gift of wine, 1896 Mar 14
    - Cooper, Sara B., 1890-1896 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - ALS thanks for gift, enclosing photograph, Nov 21, 1890
      - ALS appreciation of opening day ceremonies, Oct 3, 1891
      - ALS religious thoughts, coming to LSJU commencement, June 13, 1892
      - ALS would like to see her, Sep 17, 1893
      - ALS friends delighted with Palo Alto, death of Mrs. Dutton, would like her to be vice president of "Congress Auxiliary", Mar 10 1894
      - ALS thinking of her on anniversary of Leland's death, June 22, 1894
      - ALS sending letter of Susan B. Anthony's, Mar 31, 1895
      - ALS congratulations, RR passes for Miss Anthony and Miss Shaw will be of help, Mar 3 1896
    - Covert, Dot, 1888-1895 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - ALS J.L.Stanford has given them house in Albany, house needs work, Apr 15 1888
      - Anna Hewes' death and funeral, Mr. Hewes and Chas. Lathrop, Aug 17 1892
      - the Stanfords in Europe, Aug 28, 1892
      - death of Leland Stanford, July 11, [1893]
      - condition of Lathrop plot in cemetery, July 25, [1893]
      - congratulations, Albany news, Ariel's illness, June 30 [1895]
    - Crocker, Charles, 1894-1897 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - ALS. Indignant at C P Huntington's letter, 1894 Jan 19
      - TLS. Gage representing her interests in RR; relates current telegrams, 1894 Feb 16
      - LS and cvr. P. I. Co. obligations and Jane's position, 1894 Sep 5
      - ALS. congratulations on legal decision, 1895 June 30
      - ALS. Regrets misunderstanding, 1896 Mar 18
      - TL (copy) to R. J. Wilson. re Mexican International RR Co., 1897 Jan 11
      - ALS. Mexican International bonds., 1897 Jan 26
    - Crocker, George, 1896-1899 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Tel. congratulations, 1896 Mar 2
      - TLS. P.I. Co. matters., 1899 Nov 15
      - TLS. Control of P. I. Co.; includes copy of letter from Thos. E. Stillman, 1899 Dec. 6, re P.I. proxy, Huntington a dangerous man, bonded indebtedness of Mexican International RR Co., 1899 Dec 14
      - TLS. Crocker to be elected president of P.I. Co. [signature cut out], 1899 Dec 19
    - Crothers, George E., 1901-1904 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - ALS. re. his discussion with Mr. Lieb., 24-Oct-01
      - ALS. re. copy of university grants and amendments., 6-Nov-01
      - ALS. re. Crother's appt. as trustee; future Medical School, Mar 21, 1902
      - ALS re thanks for gift, 23-Dec-02
      - ALS. re. a program of the "Act providing for determination of validity and legal effect of grants, etc. through the legislature", 30-Jan-03
      - ALS, re. inventory of university property; copies of E.A. Ross letters., June 4, 1903
      - ALS publications nearly ready, May 29, 1903
      - ALS trustee matters, June 4, 1903
      - ALS, re. library plans, publication of first Trustees Manual, work on "Articles of Organization.", 20-Dec-03
      - ALS. re work on "Articles of Organization"; opinion of Trustees that Pres. Jordan should seek Board permission before leaving on trips away from the university., 28-Dec-03
      - ALS trustee matters, July 9, 1904
      - ALS. re. responsibility of Trustees., July 12, 1904
      - ALS re Aug. 1 meeting of Trustees, July 18, 1904
      - ALS birthday greetings, 25-Aug-04
      - ALS. re. Trustee Wm. Stewart and the difficulties of obtaining a quorum at trustee meetings; with copy of letter from Stewart to Horace Davis, 22-Sep-04
    - Couper, William, 1890-1891 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - ALS. send photographs, July 17, 1890
      - ALS. re sphinxes, family group statue, Aug 12, 1890
      - ALS. re. tomb and sphinxes., Sept 23, 1890
      - ALS. re. sphinxes., April 6, 1891
      - ALS. re. sphinxes., May 25, 1891
      - AL. mss. copy of letter to Couper re shipping sphinxes [author unknown - not J.L. Stanford or Leland Stanford], Aug 21, 1891
      - ALS. re. statue of Prof. Schliemann, sphinxes., Sep 9, 1891
      - ALS. re. sphinxes., Sep 25, 1891
      - ALS. re. sphinxes; family group statue., Nov 7, 1891
      - ALS. re. sphinxes., Nov 25, 1891
    - Ca, 1893-1902 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - California girls "Cornell", Tel. congratulations, Mar 3, 1896
      - Camm, Bertha, ALS thanks for your aid, Jan 9, 1893
      - Campbell, Georgine, ALS photos, Bonuat portrait, undated
      - Campbell, Mary Grafton, ALS praise for University from middle-aged student, sympathy for Mrs. Stanford, Feb 15, 1896
      - Carlisle, John G., ALS wine received, Dec 30, 1895
      - Carlisle, M.J., ALS thanks for flowers, Apr 2 1893?
      - Carnegie, Andrew, ALS to call, 11-Jan-02
      - Carolan, Evelyn, ALS thanks for gift (dishes), undated
      - Castle, Charlotte, ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 3, 1896
      - Castle, Matilda L., A.N.S. congratulations, undated
      - Castro, Isabel, ALS re picture of Fr. Junipero she sent Mrs. Stanford, 1902 June 17
      - Catherwood, Clinton, Tel. congratulations, Mar 3, 1896
      - Catherwood [Catnerwood], Jennie S., ALS (2) personal notes, undated
      - Catherwood, Mrs., ALS. coming to University Wednesday, May 26, ny
    - Ce - Cl, 1893-1902 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Center, Alexander, Pacific Mail Steamship Company, passage on to Japan reserved for Jane, 1902 Apr 15
      - Chandler, John Ries, ALS congratulations on the University, Sep 12 1895
      - Chandler, Katherine (Mrs. Jefferson), 2 ALS congratulations on government suit, July 11, [1895]
      - Chapman, Elizabeth, Tel. congratulations, Mar 3, 1896
      - Clarke, A.L., Tel. decision of Supreme Court, Mar 2 1896
      - Clarke, Letitia, ALS congrats. From Mrs. Stranahan, Mar 17, 1896
      - Clarkson, Anna H., personal news, congratulations on government suit, ALS Jan 24, 1896; Mar 15, 1896
      - Clements, Isaac, thanks for sending memorial book on Leland Stanford to Cazenovia Seminary, 1895 Feb
      - Clements, M. Redding, regarding her dismissal from position at Roble Hall, 1896 Dec 28 and 29
    - Coe - Cor, 1891-1902 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Coe, Katharine W., LS praise for establishing University, Feb 14, 1891
      - Colonial Dames of America, invitation to apply for membership s. Joanna Maynard Wright, Mar 6 1902
      - Colson, W (?), National Fine Arts Company, painting by Benj. West for sale, 1898 Aug 16
      - Colton, Lella Lee, ALS visit to Palo Alto, etc.; mother was in Port Washington, Feb 23, 1895
      - Combs, Ida, ALS praise and appreciation, Oct 15, 1894
      - Convent of the Holy Family, Sister Dolores, ALS personal notes and thanks, Jan 6, 1894 and Feb 8, 1896
      - Cooper, Cyrus B., ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 3 1896
      - Copeland, Clement A., ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 4, 1896
      - Copeland, H. M., TLS enclosing financial report, 1902 Mar 14
      - Corning, Mary Parker, Tel. congratulations on government suit, Mar 4 1896
      - Cortelyou, George B., LS and cvr. thank you note for Mrs. McKinley, June 14, 1901
      - Cortelyou, George B., TLS and cvr. (holograph) acknowledgement for Mrs. McKinley, July 30, 1901
    - Cot - Cz, 1891-1901 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Cotton, Aylett R. Jr., ALS all congrats on decisions in government suit, Jul 13, 1895; Oct 15, 1895; Mar 2, 1896
      - Court, James, ALS encloses draft of $100 from Albert Judson, 1893 Sep 7
      - Covert, Mary A., Tel. congratulations, July 1, 1895
      - Covey, F. W., ALS Palo Alto Stock Farm affairs, thanks for tickets, 1895 Feb 12, 1900 Mar 30
      - Cox, Chas. E., ALS congratulations, work of University can go on, Mar 2, 1896
      - Coxhead, Edith M., ALS congratulations on government suit, appreciation of University, Aug 13, 1895; Mar 3, 1896
      - Crocker, Ethel, A.N.S. congratulations on government suit, Mar 1896
      - Crosby, C. H., thanks for portraits of trustees, has valuable painting she might like to buy, 1890 Nov 21
      - Crovat, Agnes, thanks for Christmas gifts, 1901 Dec 25
      - Crovat, P.L., Tel. and TNS congratulations on government suit; encloses Cleveland letter, Mar 2,1896; Mar 16, 1896
      - Cummings, C.H., 1891 May 15 ALS re Father Junipero statue, Tel Mar 3, 1896 congratulations on government suit Cuney, John
      - Cunningham, Carrie, ALS thanks for gift of the Quad, 1895 June 15
      - Curtis, W.G., ANS congratulations on government suit, Mar 2, 1896
    - Dahlgren, Madeline, 1893-1894 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - ALS condolence, Oct 31, 1893
      - ALS Christmas wish, Dec 14, 1893
      - ALS has written Bishop Keane letter of introduction to Jane, Feb 20, 1894
    - Davis, Horace, 1896-1904 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 5, 1896
      - TLS resigns from Trust [Trustees?], recommends Frank J. Symmes, 17-Aug-04
    - Dawes, 1894-1896 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Dawes, Anna L., ALS RR strike, personal and family news, Sep 8, 1894
      - Dawes, Anna L., ALS with father in Arkansas for Indian Territory Commission work with Choctaw Nation, Nov 13, 1895
      - Dawes, Eleeta S., ALS family news, Jan 26, 1894
      - Dawes, Eleeta S., ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 4 1896
      - Dawes, H.L., Tel. congratulations from entire family, Mar 4, 1896
    - Dent, Annie B., 1891-1896 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - ALS quilt of U.S. Grant's mother, would Mrs. Stanford like to purchase for museum, Oct 1, 1891
      - ANS quilt make by Gen. Grant's mother and presented to Mrs. Dent in 1882, Nov 25, 1891
      - congratulations on government suit, explains financial troubles, Mar 7, 1896
      - going to Klondike, wants to borrow money, Nov 16, ny
    - Dimmick, Mary Scott, 1891-1893 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - ALS and cvr. introducing Mary V. Moore, artist, ny Jul 8
      - ALS Calif. visit, Menlo Park, ny May 3
      - ALS Mrs. Harrison invites Stanfords to call, undated
      - ALS accepts invitation, ny Jan 17
      - ALS Mrs. Harris invites Stanfords to call, ny May 8
      - ALS accepts dinner invitation to meet Pres. Harrison and his wife, 1891 Apr 26
      - ALS and cvr. thanks for plan of tree planting at Menlo home, 1891 June 17
      - ALS letter of introduction to Miss Moire, an artist, [1891] July 8
      - ALS and ticket Mrs. Harrison sends admission ticket, 1892 Feb 9
      - ALS and cvr. Personal, nomination of Pres. Harrison, 1892 July 2
      - ALS personal, illness of Russell Harrison's child, part of White House quarantined, 1893 Jan 2
    - Dodge family (San Francisco), 1895-1896 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Dodge, H.L., ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 2, 1896
      - Dodge, Omira B., ALS received her kind thoughts, hopes to see her soon, Jan 6, 1895
      - Dodge, Omira B., ALS congratulations on government suit, June 30, [1895]
    - Dominican College, San Rafael, 1890-1896 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Louis, Sister (M. Superior of Dominican College in San Raphael), ALS re RR pass, Jan 15, 1895, Jan 21, 1895 and Mar 12, 1896
    - Douty, F. S., 1896-1900 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 2, 1896
      - TNS re RR bonds, 1900 Apr 4
    - Da, 1893-1902 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Dart, Walter C., ALS accounts at Vina are correct, 1898 June 9
      - Daughters of the American Revolution, ALS thanks for contribution to Portrait Fund, signed by Ellen Hardin Walworth, July 31, 1894
      - Davison, Henry, ALS encloses copy of Godey's Magazine, would like article from her, 1893 May 12
      - Day, Clinton, TEL re shipping photograph stand, 1902 Feb 3 and 4
      - Dayan, Mattie [I], ALS University Ave. improvements, asks for plants, Mar 16, 1896
    - De - Di, 1888-1902 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Dean, Bradford, missed seeing her [with enclosure: letter of introduction from David Starr Jordan, Oct. 20, 1902], 1902 Nov 15
      - DeMott, Ada E., TL [15 year old girl writes to her after reading about her in paper], Jan 1, 1894
      - Dennis, Mrs. S.W.. inscribed calling card, 1895
      - Depew, Mrs. Chauncey (C.), ALS asks aid for Hahnemann Hospital, Feb 21, 1888
      - Dermot, Mary E., ALS thanks for having her husband placed in his former position with RR Co., July 14, 1895
      - Di Cesnola, L. [P.], ANS congratulations on government suit, Mar 2, 1896
      - Dickey, M.A., Congratulations from a deaf-mute ALS, Aug 21, 1895
    - Do, 1891-1898 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Dodge, Melissa P. (Mrs. William E.), ALS personal notes, congratulations on government suit, Mar 16, 1896
      - Dole, Annie W., ALS indignant on her behalf regarding government claim on Leland Stanford's estate, June 26, 1894
      - Dolph, J.N., ANS congratulations on government suit, Oct 15, 1895
      - Dooley, Edmond, ALS would like to meet with her about his book "Benefactions and Benefactors of California", 1893 July 24
      - Dorsey, Anna Hansen, ALS personal, son killed in Civil War, Dec 24, 1891
      - Dorsey, Rebecca Lee, ALS requesting money to start hospital for women and children in Los Angeles, 1893 Aug 26
      - Douglas, Maria A., ALS expresses support for Mrs. Stanford, Feb 9, 1896; Mar 4, 1896
      - Douthat, R. W.,ALS would like her to be patron of his book, 1893 Aug 30
      - Doyle, John, ALS she has no power (based on foundation deed) to displace Dr. Taylor, 1898 June 14
    - Edmunds, Susan Marsh (Mrs. George F.), 1892-1896 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - ANS invites her to lunch, ny Jan 15
      - ALS wishes Stanfords good trip back to America, 1892 Sep 26
      - ALS thanks for present, Jan 25, 1896
      - AN best wishes, undated
    - E, 1891-1896 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Earl, Mr. and Mrs. D. W., inscribed card congratulations, Mar 2, 1896
      - Easton, Adeline, ALS accepting invitation for opening day ceremonies, Sep 13, 1891
      - Easton, Louise A., ALS thanks for book, relates story of her son's death, Mar 21 ny
      - Eaton, John, TLS congratulations on government suit, Mar 3, 1896
      - Edwards, Mary, ALS re packing up of Washington house, 1893 Sep 11
      - Elliot, John F., ALS expresses appreciation for Sen. Stanford's help in releasing him from San Quentin, has written book of poetry that he would like to dedicate to Mrs. Stanford; includes mss of poem, 1893 July 15
      - Evans, Frank, Geo. S. and Wilson B., Tel. congratulations on government suit, Mar 3, 1896
      - Ewell, Edwin, ALS thanks for RR pass, 1895 Jan 4
      - Examiner, The, TEL rumor you are selling jewels; includes negative answer from Mrs. Stanford, undated
    - Flint, Annie G., 1895 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - ALS collection for museum, Oct 1, 1895
      - ALS received gift of book "Imitation of Christ"; relates her own tragedy, Oct 4, 1895
      - ALS congratulations on government suit, Oct 14, 1895
    - Flood, Jennie C., 1888-1889 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - ALS re her father's illness, Oct 7, 1888
      - more on father's illness, other personal notes, Dec 2, 1888
      - death of father, preparations for funeral, Feb 27, 1889
      - ANS on card, Mar 20, 1889?
    - Fa - Fl, 1892-1896 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Farquhar, A.B., 2 Tels. both congratulations on government suit, Jul 1, 1895; Mar 2, 1896
      - Farr, Lorin, ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 4, 1896
      - Ferguson, L. C., ALS encloses bill for Palo Alto Stock Farm repair; suggests course of action re certain properties, 1893 Sep 8
      - Ferguson, L. C., ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 6 1896
      - Field, Mrs. J. V., ALS enjoyed her visit with Mrs. Stanford, July 29, 1891
      - Field, Mrs. J. V., ALS going East, looks forward to future visits, Aug 18, 1891
      - Field, Stephan J., Tel. congratulations, Mar 3, 1896
      - Field, Stephany, TL resigning as regent of University to avoid conflict of interest ["Stephany" is probably typing error for "Stephen J"], 1894 Oct 15
      - Field, Sue V., ALS congratulations, undated
      - Fielder, Belle (Pres. of Roble), ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 3, 1896
      - Fitch, Mary T., ALS similarity of lives, Feb 3, 1892
      - Fitzgerald, Mrs. H. L., ALS re mineral collection for sale, 1893 July 11
      - Flood, Cora Jane, ALS invites Gov. and Mrs. Stanford to lunch, undated
    - Fo - Fr, 1887-1896 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Folsom, E.C., ALS from Exec. Mansion thanks for tickets, Jan 23, 1887
      - Fonte, Mary de (K.), ALS sends Christmas present, undated
      - Fonte, R.C., Tel. and ALS congratulations on government suit, Jul 1, 1895; Oct 12, 1895
      - Foote, Henry S., ALS letter of support, Mar 8, 1896
      - Forrest, R.F., ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 3, 1896
      - Foster, Mary Parke, ALS congratulations on government suit, 1896 Mar 3
      - Foster, William J., ALS sending pictures of his family; best wishes, Dec 28, 1893
      - [Fouts], M., ALS lost husband, June 18, 1893
      - Frank, Day, ALS congratulations on government suit, Mar 3, 1896
      - Fresh, M.S., ALS congratulations, wants loan, Mar 1896?
    - Gage, S.T., 1890-1895 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - TLS re Father Junipero statue, 1890 Dec 19
      - TLS re. Museum building, Father Junipero statue, 1890 Dec 27
      - TLS re. adoption case, Museum construction, statue of Junipero Serra, Gage's testimony on Murphy vs. Mahoney; includes ALS by W. T. Adel, Western Granite and Marble Co. re statue, 1891 Jan 2
      - TLS re. Museum construction, contacts of its cornerstone box, election of Leland Stanford to 2nd term as Senator., 1891 Jan 14
      - ALS congratulations, Mrs. Gage ill, 1895 Oct 14
    - Gardner, D. Charles, 1901-1904 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - ALS re. Memorial Church murals and inscriptions., circa 1901
      - ALS re. Memorial Church programs, activities as Chaplain, death of a student, tourists admiring campus buildings, 1904 Mar 17
    - Gilmore, 1894-1896 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Gilmore, Eleanor E. ALS anxious to see her, Feb 1895
      - Gilmore, Eleanor E. ALS daughter Grace, Mar 25, 1895
      - Gilmore, Eleanor E. Easter greetings, Apr 13, 1895
      - Gilmore, Grace H., ALS working in D.C., Dec 16, 1894
      - Gilmore, Grace H., ALS clerking in Pension Office, Apr 7, 1895
      - Gilmore, Grace H., ALS sorry to hear Mr. Nash ill, worried about keeping her position, Apr 11, 1895
      - Gilmore, Grace H., ALS congratulations on government suit, still has her position, Mar 4, 1896
    - Gould, Elizabeth Porter, 1894-1903 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - ALS visit to University, interest in kindergartens, friend of Miss Peabody, Dec 13, 1894
      - ALS congratulations and support, Mar 2, 1896
      - ALS thanks for gift, invitation to visit when in Boston, her own work, June 20, 1903
    - Grant family, 1890-1899 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Grant, Fannie C. (Mrs. Ulysses Jr.)
        - ALS invitation to country, Dec 19, 1890
        - ALS to call at Palo Alto, Apr 4 1891
        - ALS leaving for the east, Apr 13, 1891
      - Grant, Jesse R. calling card and clip. re: Tia Jauna gambling concession, undated
      - Grant, Julia (daughter of F.D.G.)
        - ALS thanks for watch, cholera danger, Sep 6, 1892
        - ALS seasonal greetings, Jan 10, 1895
        - ALS engagement to Prince [Cantacuzene] of Russia, May, 1899
        - ALS (New York) regrets not seeing her, renewed thanks for the watch, undated
      - Grant, L.M.C.
        - 2 ALS invit. to dine with Mrs. [U.S.] Grant, undated
        - moving to Piedmont, Dec 1 ny
      - Grant, U.S. Jr.
        - ALS taking his mother to country, offers use of horse and carriage to Stanfords, undated
        - ALS to see Sutro's new baths, Apr 19, 1895
        - ALS forwarding of letter from Mrs. Grant, running for Senate, Herrin and RR opposition., Jan 21, 1899
    - Grant, Frederick Dent, 1889-1894 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - ALS trying for mission to China, Mar 12, 1889
      - ALS checks on antiques for J. L. Stanford, Sep 17, 1890
      - ALS received draft for antiques, Sep 21 1890
      - ALS and cvr. re: L.S.J.U. "Hereditary Prince", Nov 8, 1891
      - ALS condolences on death of Sen. Stanford, Jan 19, 1894
      - calling card with invitation to attend church, undated
    - Grant, Ida
      - 1884-1886 (Box 4, Folder 27)
        - ALS newspaper accounts of Grant - Vanderbilt correspondence, undated
        - ALS our boy Ulysses, ny Dec 10
        - ALS regrets invite, leaving D.C., undated
        - ALS sorry she missed her in New York, undated
        - ALS Gen'l Grant's stenographer would serve Stanfords, undated
        - ALS warm regards, undated
        - ALS asking job for Col. Grant with RR, possible RR in Turkey, staying with Gen and Mrs. Grant, 1884, Aug 1
        - ALS Gen'l and Mrs. Grant enjoyed visit with Stanfords, Col. Grant would welcome position with RR in the west, 1884, Sep 6
        - ALS writing for Mrs. Grant, burial of Leland Jr. and Dr. Newman's sermon, Gen. Grant's illness, 1885, Feb 17
        - ALS Grant's illness and remedies, 1885, Mar 20
        - ALS thank you from Mrs. Grant, 1885, June 5
        - ALS effect of death of Gen Grant, 1885, Aug 15
        - ALS writing for Mrs. Grant, invites Mrs. Stanford to visit her in cottage at Elberon, 1886, June 20
      - 1887-1889 (Box 4, Folder 28)
        - ALS Mrs. Logan, 1887, Jan 1